<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R-Ladies Philly</title>
    <link>http://rladiesphilly.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on R-Ladies Philly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rladiesphilly.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>May recap: Git happieR with GitHub</title>
      <link>http://rladiesphilly.org/2018/05/22/may-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rladiesphilly.org/2018/05/22/may-recap/</guid>
      <description>Our May Event! The May R-Ladies meetup took place on May 16, 2018 at Drexel’s LeBow School of Business. Thanks for hosting us again, Drexel, and thanks to our sponsors Datacamp and the R consortium!
Our topic for May was version control using the popular resources Git and GitHub, and we focused on integrating version control with R.
 Intro Darina and I started with an example to illustrate the utility of version control in collaborating on a document or project over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April recap: Introduction to Text Mining with R</title>
      <link>http://rladiesphilly.org/2018/04/29/april-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rladiesphilly.org/2018/04/29/april-recap/</guid>
      <description>Our April Event! The April R-Ladies meetup was held on April 19th at Drexel. Thanks again to Drexel for hosting us and to DataCamp and the R consortium for sponsoring us!
Our topic was an introduction to text mining in R using the first two chapters of “Text Mining with R” by fellow R-Lady(!) Julia Silge and David Robinson.
There was a great group - including some new faces!
 Amy took us through the key concepts of the chapter and then we broke into groups to do some exercises together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who are the Philly R-Ladies? Analyzing Data from Google Forms</title>
      <link>http://rladiesphilly.org/2018/03/11/survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rladiesphilly.org/2018/03/11/survey/</guid>
      <description>Why do a new member survey? Step One: Get the data from google to R Step Two: Make some plots My takeaways   Why do a new member survey? One of the goals of R-Ladies Philly is for the group to be focused on the needs and interests of its members. With this goal in mind, we created a survey to query members about meeting logistics and R experience level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the R-Ladies Philly blog!</title>
      <link>http://rladiesphilly.org/2018/03/07/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rladiesphilly.org/2018/03/07/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Hello and thank you for visiting our brand-new R-Ladies Philly blog! For our first post, we are introducing the founding principles of our chapter and our goals moving forward. With that in mind, if you R ready, here we go!
As you may already know, R-Ladies Philly is a chapter of the broader R-Ladies global organization. R-Ladies global seeks to promote gender diversity in the coding community by providing a collaborative network of R learners, mentors, and leaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://rladiesphilly.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rladiesphilly.org/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; example website for the blogdown package. The theme was forked from @jrutheiser/hugo-lithium-theme and modified by Yihui Xie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>